[
  {
    "question": "What are the keywords in the definition of software architecture in the textbook?",
    "answers": [0, 1, 2, 3],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": [
      "Software components",
      "Properties",
      "Structures",
      "Relationships"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "A representation of a whole system from the perspective of a related set of concerns is called?",
    "answers": [3],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": [
      "Architectural description",
      "Architectural pattern",
      "Software architecture",
      "Architectural view"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What standard is used for software architectural documentation in this course?",
    "answers": [1],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": ["ISO 900", "IEEE 1471", "IEEE 1990", "ARCH 1400"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What types of views are described in the textbook?",
    "answers": [0, 1, 3],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": ["Allocation", "Component-and-Connector", "Dynamic", "Module"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What view mainly addresses the developers and the project managers?",
    "answers": [0],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": ["Development", "Logical", "Process", "Physical"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What view is most relevant for the end user?",
    "answers": [1],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": [
      "Developer view",
      "Logical view",
      "Process view",
      "Physical view"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What view represents an abstraction of the most important requirements?",
    "answers": [3],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": ["Development", "Logical", "Process", "Scenario"]
  },
  {
    "question": "In what view can ER-modelling typically be used?",
    "answers": [1],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": ["Development", "Logical", "Physical", "Scenario"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What view has the main focus on non-functional requirements such as availability & scalability?",
    "answers": [2, 3],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": [
      "Development view",
      "Logical view",
      "Process view",
      "Physical view"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What characteristics should be identified when going from the logical to process view?",
    "answers": [0, 1, 2, 3],
    "exam": ".*",
    "options": ["Autonomy", "Distribution", "Persistance", "Subordination"]
  }
]
